Sons, lock up your fathers... Vengeance arrives on... Father's Day!
Father's Day is a action, comedy, horror film directed by Adam Brooks.
Ahab, a man obsessed with exacting a brutal, violent revenge on the man who murdered his dad, joins John, an eager priest, and Twink, a
hot-headed street hustler, on an epic quest to find and defeat this mythical monster known as Chris Fuchman AKA The Father's Day Killer.
Ahab, played by Adam Brooks.
Father John Sullivan, played by Matthew Kennedy.
Twink, played by Conor Sweeney.
Chelsea, played by Amy Groening.
Walnut, played by Garrett Hnatiuk.
Detective Stegel, played by Brent Neale.
Father's Day is a 2011 action-horror comedy film directed by Adam Brooks, Jeremy Gillespie,
Matthew Kennedy, Steven Kostanski and Conor Sweeney (collectively known as Astron-6).
The film stars Brooks as Ahab, a man determined to exact revenge on Chris Fuchman, the
Father's Day Killer, a rapist and serial killer who murdered his father years ago.
Originally made as a short film, the feature-length version had its world premiere on October 21,
2011 at the Toronto After Dark Film Festival, where it received multiple awards.
A documentary detailing the film's production process entitled No Sleep, No Surrender
was teased in 2012 (although it has yet to be officially released).
Despite being produced and distributed by Troma Entertainment, it
bears no relation to Mother's Day or its 2010 remake.
The film explores themes of suicide, homophobia, necrophilia, gore, revenge.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.